<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Krushi Sanjivini</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">krishisanjeevini1@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>

    <string name="menu_language">Choose Langauge</string>
    <string name="menu_call_helpline">Call Helpline</string>
    <string name="menu_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="menu_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="updateat">Updated at</string>
    <string name="clearsky">Clear Sky</string>
    <string name="tempreture">24oC</string>
    <string name="mintemp">Min temp</string>
    <string name="address">Location</string>
    <string name="title_activity_crop_plot_registration">CropPlotRegistration</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->

    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>


    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="name">username</string>
    <string name="email">email</string>
    <string name="passWord">Password</string>
    <string name="confirm_passWord">confirm password</string>
    <string name="btRegister">regiter</string>
    <string name="btn_link_to_login">Login</string>
    <string name="label_signup">Sign Up </string>
    <string name="phoneno">Mobile No</string>
    <string name="farm_id">Plot ID:</string>
    <string name="farmer_name">Farmers Name:</string>
    <string name="farmer_last_name">Farmers Last Name:</string>
    <string name="farmer_address">Farmers Address:</string>
    <string name="farmer_taluqa">Farmers Taluqa:</string>
    <string name="farmers_district">Farmers District:</string>
    <string name="farmers_state">Farmers State:</string>
    <string name="crop_name">Crop Name:</string>
    <string name="crop_variety">Crop Variety:</string>
    <string name="crop_season">Crop Season:</string>
    <string name="choose_date">Choose Date:</string>
    <string name="water_source">Water Source:</string>
    <string name="soil_type">Soil Type:</string>
    <string name="intention">Intention:</string>
    <string name="crop_distance">Crop Distance:</string>
    <string name="distanceTo">X</string>
    <string name="age_of_plant">Age of the plant:</string>
    <string name="total_area">Total Area(Acres):</string>
    <string name="payment_status">Payment Status:</string>
    <string name="pruning_date">Pruning Date:</string>
    <string name="select_district">Select District:</string>
    <string name="select_taluqa">Select Taluqa:</string>
    <string name="village_name">Name of your Village:</string>
    <string name="full_address">Your full address:</string>
    <string name="payment_label">Do you want to make the payment now? then click below button:</string>
    <string name="make_payment">Make Payment</string>
    <string name="trail_label">If you wish to take a 10 days trial then press submit button:</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="user_phone_no">Phone No of the farmer</string>
    <string name="refered_phone_no">Refereed Phone No</string>
    <string name="accept_policy">I Promise that I will be abide and agree by the app terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="enter_otp">Please Enter the O T P</string>
    <string name="send_otp">Send OTP</string>
    <string name="enter_otp_here">Enter OTP here</string>
    <string name="present_crop_period">Present Crop Period</string>
    <string name="my_plot_schedule">My plot Today’s Schedule</string>
    <string name="weather_report">Weather Report</string>
    <string name="ask_question">Your Question our Answer</string>
    <string name="knowledge_bank">Knowledge Bank</string>
    <string name="webinar">Webinar</string>
    <string name="videos">Videos for You</string>
    <string name="agree_dealer">Agri Input Dealer</string>
    <string name="service_provider">Service Provider</string>
    <string name="my_diary">My Diary</string>
    <string name="my_plot_details">My plot Details</string>
    <string name="select_plot_details">Select plot </string>
    <string name="register_another_plot">Register your Another Plot</string>
    <string name="network_info">Please check your network/internet connection</string>
    <string name="diary_title">Diary Title</string>
    <string name="diary_details">You can right diary details here</string>
    <string name="diary_unit">Unit</string>
    <string name="diary_phi">PHI</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="diary_diseage">Diseage Information</string>
    <string name="save_diary">Save</string>
    <string name="schedule_day">Schedule Day:</string>
    <string name="after_pronningdays">Before Pronning Days:</string>
    <string name="medicine_details">Medicine Brand:</string>
    <string name="active_ingredients">Active Ingredients:</string>
    <string name="disease_Infection">Disease Infection:</string>
    <string name="view_schedule">View Schedule</string>
    <string name="schedule">Schedule</string>
    <string name="no_schedule">Schedule is not available for this plot</string>
    <string name="no_questions">There is no any data availabel</string>
    <string name="record_voice">Record Voice</string>
    <string name="record_play">Play Voice</string>
    <string name="record_stop">Stop Recording</string>
    <string name="schedule_date">Schedule Date:</string>
    <string name="spray_medicine_brand">Spray Medicine Brand:</string>
    <string name="request_title">Question Title:</string>
    <string name="question_date">Requested Date:</string>
    <string name="question_assigned">Assigned To:</string>
    <string name="question_status">Request Status:</string>
    <string name="answer">Answer:</string>
    <string name="raise_request">Ask Question</string>
    <string name="view_questions_list">View Status</string>
    <string name="ques_title">You found any problem or diseage information for your farm you can click on Ask Question button to register problem</string>
    <string name="status_title">For tracking status of your question, please click on View Status button </string>
    <string name="notification">Notifications</string>
    <string name="select_state">Select Your State :</string>
    <string name="about_us_title">KRISHI SANJEEVINI is experienced team of agribusiness professionals engaged in grape advisory, plantation and cultivation. Over a period of time, KRISHI SANJEEVINI has developed expertise in cultivation and quality harvesting aspects of grape industry. KRISHI SANJEEVINI is serving grape community using strong technical knowledge and providing timely practical solutions with respect to cultivation as well as processing of resins of grapes. KRISHI SANJEEVINI dedicated working teem mainly focusing on cultivation practices, nutrition management, pest and disease management, quality and yield management and solutions to cultivation related issues. We have also developed and launched KRISHI SANJEEVINI Android agricultural Application exclusively for grape growers to provide timely advisory on cultivation aspects and real time problem solving. To serve the grape industry better, . We have started a dedicated YouTube channel, KRISHI SANJEEVINI Agri Services through which the farmers will be guided through the guidance video for the current issues and solutions.</string>
    <string name="call_label">Call :+918352317645 </string>
    <string name="call_email">krishisanjeevini1@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">1001</string>
    <string name="spray_schedule">Spray Schedule:</string>
    <string name="spray_ingredients">Ingredients:</string>
    <string name="spray_purpose">Purpose:</string>
    <string name="basal_dose_note" >Basal Dose Note:</string>
    <string name="basal_dose_medicine">Basal Medicine Brand:</string>
    <string name="basal_ingredients">Basal Ingredients:</string>
    <string name="basal_purpose">Basal Purpose:</string>
    <string name="notes_data">Notes:</string>

    <string name="weather_activity">Weather Report</string>
    <string name="question_activity">Question and Answer</string>
    <string name="askquestion">Ask Question</string>
    <string name="register_your_plot">Register your Plot</string>
    <string name="username">Enter Name</string>
    <string name="read_accept">Yes I Have Read</string>
    <string name="privacy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy"><![CDATA[This Privacy Policy governs the privacy terms of the Application called Krishi Sanjeevini , which is owned and operated by Krishi Sanjeevini (“Company”). The Application is an integrated online platform consisting of the Company’s platform offering agronomy advisory , awareness of the agriculture products, designed to meet individual farmer’s and agribusiness need and offered by the Company on subscription basis (the &quot;Application&quot;). The Services offered on this Application are provided through both online and offline means by the Company For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, the terms &quot;we&quot;, “our” and &quot;us&quot; refers to Company and its affiliates, and the term &quot;you&quot;, “your” or the “user” refers to you, the users downloading or accessing the Application by themselves or on your behalf of a company or any other legal entity and who is creating its account on the Application in accordance with the Terms of Use. If you are entering into these Terms on behalf of a company or other legal entity, you represent that you haves the authority to bind such entity to the terms and conditions of these Terms and, in such an event your use of this Application shall refer to use by such legal entity. If you do not have such an authority or do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, then you should refrain from using this Application. We respect the privacy of everyone who uses the Application. This Privacy Policy describes the procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your Personal Information (defined below) which you exchange with us, directly or indirectly for availing the Services or accessing the Application. We recommend you to read this Privacy Policy to understand our approach towards the use of your Personal Information. When you access or use the Application, you agree to our Privacy Policy and consent to our collection, storage, transfer, processing use, disclosure and other uses of your Personal Information (defined below) as described in this Privacy Policy. You understand and acknowledge that you are required to provide the Personal Information when you choose to avail the Services. Thank you for visiting our apps. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the apps, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this apps only. If you link to other apps, please review the privacy policies posted at those apps. Collection of Information.We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. By submitting your email address, you are giving us permission to add you to our e-newsletter list. Commitment to Data Security Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this apps allow you to opt out of further mailings. Access to the application Our Application is not aimed at Users under 18 years of age and we will not directly collect, use, provide or process in any other form any Personal Information of user under the age of 18 years deliberately. We therefore also ask you, if you are under 18 years old, to not send us your Personal Information (for example, your name, address) and to not access our Application. In addition to being of the minimum required age to use our Application under applicable law, if you are not old enough to have authority to agree to our Terms in your country, your parent or guardian must agree to our Terms on your behalf. Applicable law This Privacy Policy is governed by the provisions of the Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules 2011, which is designed to protect Personal Information; other relevant laws, and the Company policies effective and applicable during the term you avail the Services. How we use personal information The Personal Information is collected and used to: (i) provide or operate Services; (ii) create and administer your accounts/User Profile and to improve the quality and your experience, of the Application and Services, including but not limited to conducting audits and resolving your issues; (iii) customize, improve our Services; (iv) to analyse service related diagnostic and performance information (v) providing information of events conducted in the local areas, as per location information (vi) manage our relationship with you and develop our present and future Services; (vii) maintain and update our records; (viii) monitor suspected fraud(s), misconduct(s) and unlawful activities and safety and security on the Application. We will not sell, exchange or disclose your information to or with any third party without your consent, except as provided for in this Privacy Policy. We may also collect Personal Information when you interact with our customer service in order to assist you and to improve the operation of the Application and the Services we offer. You agree that we may also use the Personal Information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted advertisements, service offerings and communications relevant to your use of the Application. By accepting this policy, you expressly agree and allow us to receive and use this Personal Information for the above stated purposes. Information we collect The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.  If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide. When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, company name, address, email address, and telephone number. Disclosures Personal Information exchanged with Public: As a default setting, the Personal Information you exchange is only exchanged with or displayed for the Users with whom you have connected or with whom you interact through the Application. However, in the event you chose to exchange the Personal Information with public at large, your Personal Information shall be displayed on the Application and shall be visible to any and all users or visitors of the Application. In the event, you choose to exchange your Personal Information with public, it shall be available to anyone who has availed or not availed our Services and can be seen or accessed through online search engines or offline media. Information exchanged with other Users: Your Personal Information may be exchanged, re-exchanged, uploaded or displayed by the other users (“Disclosing User”), in such an event the users connected to such Disclosing User or the audience which such Disclosing User chooses, will have access to your Personal Information. In the event, you exchange Personal Information in any group of which you are part of, all the group members of such group shall have access to your Personal Information. Affiliates or Business Partners: We may provide Personal Information we collect, to our affiliates or our business partners through whom we provide Services to you. For example, we may disclose Personal Information to our affiliates in order to respond to your requests for information or Services. Joint Marketing Arrangements: Where permitted by law, we may exchange your Personal Information with joint marketers with whom we have a marketing arrangement, we would require all such joint marketers to have written contracts with us that specify appropriate use of your Personal Information, require them to safeguard your Personal Information. Service Providers or Business Partners: We may use certain trusted third parties and individuals to help us provide, analyse, and improve the Services or provide marketing, developing, product development or, data storage, payment processing and other features related to the Service. These third parties, including their employees, and authorized personnel may have access to your Personal Information only for purposes of performing these tasks and are under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy. We may disclose your Personal Information to service providers who perform business functions or hosting services on our behalf. Persons Who Acquire our assets or business: We may transfer or transmit your Personal Information if we are acquired by / we acquire or merge with another entity or transfer a part of our business, including the Application to a third party. Any third party or resultant entity that receives your Personal Information pursuant to a merger, demerger, reorganization, restructuring or business transfer shall have the right to continue to use your Personal Information. In the event of such a sale or transfer, we reasonably notify you. Legal and Regulatory Authorities: We may be required to disclose your Personal Information due to legal or regulatory requirements. You understand that we may have to transfer and process information subject to applicable laws in India and other countries globally where we have or use facilities, service providers, or partners regardless of the User’s location. You understand and confirm that laws, regulations and standards of the country in which your information is stored may be different from those of your country. In such instances, we reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information as required in order to comply with our legal obligations, including but not limited to complying with court orders, warrants, or discovery requests. We may also disclose your Personal Information to law enforcement officers or others, in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce this Privacy Policy; respond to claims that any Personal Information violates the rights of third-parties; or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the Company, our users or the general public. You agree and acknowledge that we may not inform you prior to or after disclosures made according to this section. You hereby agree and provide your consent to our use of your Personal Information and our practices, including the collection, use, processing, and sharing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy, as well as the transfer and processing of your information to the other service providers, affiliates or business partners, regardless of where you use our Services. Notwithstanding anything mentioned hereinabove, the Company shall not be responsible for the actions or omissions of the parties (including but not limited to the entities listed above) with whom the Personal Information is shared, nor shall the Company be responsible and/or liable for any additional information you may choose to provide directly to any third party. Cookies Our Application may use ’cookies’ to enhance User experience. Cookies are small encrypted files, that the Application transfers to your computer’s hard drive or on your mobile / tablet device or through any such electronic device through which you may access the Application through your web browser that enables the Application to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information Children’s Information Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity. Krishi Sanjeevini does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records. Data retention We will retain your Personal Information for as long as your User Profile is active or till the time we are required to provide you the Services. We may retain and use your Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreement(s) or Terms. Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your information, upon reasonable request. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting information from our servers and backed-up versions. In addition, we do not delete from our servers, the files that you have in common with other users.  Security We value your Personal Information; we will ensure an adequate level of protection to protect and secure your Personal Information from any unauthorized disclosure. We have therefore implemented technology and policies with the objective of protecting your Personal Information from unauthorized access and improper use and will update these measures as new technology becomes available, as appropriate. Your Personal Information is stored on our database which is either hosted on the private cloud or public cloud. We verify accounts and activity, and promote safety and security on and off our Services, such as by investigating suspicious activity or violations of our Terms, and to ensure our Services are being used legally. All the weblinks used are with SSL security certification domain. We have in place data administrators who check the sanity of the data. However, all the information available on the Application is on an ‘as-is’ basis and the Company shall not be held liable for any information whatsoever on the Application. As a matter of security, we take back-up of systems periodically. Although we provide appropriate firewalls and protections. Our systems are not hack proof. Data pilferage due to unauthorized hacking,virus attacks, technical issues are possible, and we take no liability or responsibility for it. We/any of our personnel never asks for any kind of transactional details including but not limited to OTP, Credit/Debit Card Details, Netbanking/Phonebanking details. In case of any loss user will be responsible by its own. You are solely responsible for all actions of your user account and password. Therefore, we do not recommend that you disclose your password to any third party. If you choose to exchange your credentials relating to the User Profile including the password or any Personal Information with third parties, you are solely responsible for the same. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your Personal Information and may be subject to legally binding actions. Interaction between you and the company We are interested in your views, and we value the Feedback (defined below) we receive from you, we therefore have set up blogs and chat rooms for providing better Services and/or to receive your feedbacks. However, we do not have control or are responsible for any such Feedback or the Personal Information which you make available through these chat rooms or the Application. We encourage you to be careful about what Personal Information you disclose in this way. Subject to any applicable law, any communication sent by you through the Application or through the blogs or chat rooms or testimonials or otherwise on the Application to us (including without limitation contents, images, audio, feedback etc. collectively &quot;Feedback&quot;) is on a non-confidential basis, and we are under no obligation to refrain from reproducing, publishing or otherwise using it in any way or for any purpose. You agree you will not assert any ownership right of any kind in the Feedback (including without limitation copyright, patent, trademark, unfair competition, moral rights, or implied contract) and you hereby irrevocably waive the right to receive any financial or other consideration in connection with the Feedback, including without limitation acknowledgment of you as the source of the Feedback. Your submission of any Feedback shall constitute an assignment to us of all worldwide rights, titles and interests in all copyrights and other intellectual property rights in the Feedback. For this reason, we ask you to not send us any Feedback that you do not wish to assign to us, including any confidential information, Personal Information or any original creative materials. You shall be responsible for the content and information contained in any Feedback sent by you to the Application or otherwise to us, including without limitation for its truthfulness and accuracy. In the event, you participate in any interactive features of the Application, participate in a survey, contest, promotion, sweepstakes, activity or event, request customer support, communicate with us via third party social media sites or otherwise communicate with us, we collect the data you submit for such participation and/or support, which may also include Personal Information. We would use such data, as per the terms of this Privacy Policy. Accessing and modifying personal information In case you need to access, remove, review, edit, and/or make changes to the Personal Information that you have provided to us, you may do so by clicking on the ‘edit’ option provided in the User Profile settings tab. You can make changes in your User Profile at any time by accessing the Application settings. You understand that the Company shall not verify or authenticate the information, or any changes made to the Personal Information made by you and therefore you take entire responsibility of such information and/ or changes. You confirm that such changes shall be in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. You can delete your User Profile any time, in such an event, we would not be required to provide you the Services. If you want to delete your User Profile at any time (including if you want to revoke your consent to our use of your information) you have to send an email requesting to delete your User Profile. Upon which we will delete your User Profile within the next three working days. You will receive a confirmation email. Third party links We may have links to other websites/ Apps of the Company or of third parties or you are referred to our Application through a link from another website /apps. We shall not be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such websites /applications. The content is subject to their terms of use and any additional guidelines and privacy information provided in relation to that use on their website / applications. If you use our Services with such third- party links we may receive information about you We recommend that you check the policy of each website / apps you visit to better understand your rights and obligations especially when you are submitting any type of content to those third-party websites. Please contact the owner or administrator or operator of such website / apps if you have any concerns or questions. Indemnification All rights not expressly granted in this Privacy Policy are reserved by the Company. Nothing contained in this Privacy Policy shall be construed as conferring by implication, estoppels or otherwise any license or right under any copyright, patent, trademark or other intellectual property right of Company or any other person or to user. Reservation of rights  All rights not expressly granted in this Privacy Policy are reserved by the Company. Nothing contained in this Privacy Policy shall be construed as conferring by implication, estoppels or otherwise any license or right under any copyright, patent, trademark or other intellectual property right of Company or any other person or to user. Limitation of liability Company will not be liable for any damages, direct or indirect, incidental or consequential, and all liabilities including for negligence, loss or damage such as loss of revenue, unavailability of system or loss of data and loss of your Personal Information and for use of or inability to use Services of any kind that is offered or to provide indemnity or any other remedy to you or any third party. Governing laws and disputes Governing Laws: This Agreement shall be construed and governed by the laws of India without regard to principles of conflict of laws. The courts in Vijayapur, India shall have an exclusive jurisdiction over any disputes arising under this policy. Dispute Resolution: Any dispute arising, shall be submitted to the arbitration to be conducted in Vijayapur , India in English language, in accordance with the rules and regulations of the Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996 (as amended from time to time), by a sole arbitrator, who shall be appointed by the Company and the award made in pursuance thereof shall be binding on the parties hereto. The dispute resolution and arbitration process mentioned in this Section will not prohibit Company from approaching the courts for appropriate interim reliefs. Changes to this policy Amendments to this policy will be posted to this Application and will be effective when posted. Your continued use of this Application following the posting of any amendment, modification, or change shall constitute your acceptance of the amendment. We request you to check this Privacy Policy on a periodic basis to ascertain if any additional considerations are involved with regard to your Personal Information.]]></string>


</resources>